Finding Aid for Engineering Communications & Marketing (University of Michigan) records 1860-2010
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan 1998
- Visual Materials
  - Photographs, Contact Sheets and Negatives
    - Historical (1860-2000)
      - Buildings
        - West & East Engineering, 1930 (Box 12)
        - West Engineering, 1903 (Box 12)
        - West Engineering Arch, Early, 1900s (Box 12)
        - West Engineering, 1889-1900s (Box 12)
      - Landmarks
        - West Engineering/ '53 "M"/Vulcan/Diag Fountain/Campus Scenes/Design for Impact Campaign, 1992 (Box 13)
        - 42e Plaza with Students, Lecture, 10/2/1991 (Box 13)
        - Engineering Vignettes/ Historical, Winter '72/Spring '73 (Box 13)
      - Centers, Institutes, Programs, Labs (C.I.P.L)
        - Caen Labs-Apollo, Lisa, 1984 (Box 13)
        - Solid State Electronic Laboratory, Miscellaneous, 1988-? (Box 13)
        - Ultrafast Optics Lab, 3/14/1989 (Box 13)
        - Ultrafast Optics Lab, Fall 1990 (Box 13)
        - Ultrafast Science, older (Box 13)
      - Events
        - Alumni Society Awards Dinner Program, 1993 (Box 13)
        - Alumni Society Awards Dinner Program, 1994 (Box 13)
        - Alumni Society Awards Dinner Program, 1995 (Box 13)
        - Art Fair, Central Campus Landmarks, 7/6/1984 (Box 13)
        - Bi-Planes over Barton Pond/ Letter to Lew Wilcoxen, 1915-1971 (Box 13)
        - Campaign Event Dinner, 9/17/1992 (Box 13)
        - Capital Campaign, 1970s (Box 13)
        - Civil Aeronautics Conference/Orville Wright/John Pawlowski, 1928 (Box 13)
        - Installation of '42e Plaza Granite Benches, 9/25/1992 (Box 13)
        - Lay Automotive Lab Dedication, 1977 (Box 13)
        - MLK Day, 1/14/1993 (Box 13)
        - Sam Wu Dinner, 4/28/1992 (Box 13)
        - Capital Campaign/Case Statement Photo Shoot negatives, 1992 (Box 13)
        - Capital Campaign/Case Statement photo shoot contact sheets, 1992 (Box 13)
        - Capital Campaign/Case Statement Slides, 1992 (Box 13)
        - Capital Campaign Joseph E. Rowe contact sheet and prints, 1992 (Box 13)
        - Capital Campaign Robert J. Vlasic contact sheet and prints, 1992 (Box 13)
      - Individuals A-Z
        - 36E Alumni, older (Box 13)
        - Angell, James B. (Former U-M President), 1880s (Box 13)
        - Ashby, Sir Eric, 1976 (Box 13)
        - Daniel Atkins, Charles Cain, Thomas Donahue, Ron Gibala, George Haddad, Walton Hancock, Emmett Leith, Demress Stockman (BSE '92), Robert J. Vlasic, Walt Weber, Chelsea White Iii, Shien-Ming "Sam" Wu / Design For Impact Campaign, 1992 (Box 13)
        - Attwood, Stephen (Box 13)
        - Bolden, Charles F. Jr., Astronaut, Not an Alumni, 1990 (Box 13)
        - Brown, Margaret (Sister of G.G. Brown), 1918 (Box 13)
        - Bush, George, President and Mrs., Graduation, 5/4/1991 (Box 13)
        - Class Officers-1915, 1916, 1917 1915-17 (Box 13)
        - Clown Professor, 1980s (Box 13)
        - Cole, Edward N., older (Box 13)
        - Cooley Mortimer E., 1879-80 (Box 13)
        - Davis, J. B., 1880s (Box 13)
        - Dodge, Professor (Box 13)
        - Engineering Shops Faculty, 1904 (Box 13)
        - Faculty Awards/ MI Engineer Cover, Spring 1991 (Box 13)
        - Ford, Gerald; Blanchard, James; Shapiro, Harold; Nederlander, Robert, Spring 1984 (Box 13)
        - G.G. Brown, 1950s (Box 13)
        - Goebel, Paul G., older (Box 13)
        - Huebner, George J., older (Box 13)
        - Steven Jobs, 1980s (Box 13)
        - G. Lawton Johnson, 1960s (Box 13)
        - James E. Knott, BSE '38 A&A, 1970s (Box 13)
        - Kodaira, Ko (Box 13)
        - Lang, Brent Olympic Medal Winner, Eng. Student, 10/31/88, 1990 (Box 13)
        - Mayer, John P., '04 BSE A&A, February 1969 (Box 13)
        - Moore (Box 13)
        - Marian Sarah Parker, circa, 1895 (Box 13)
        - Felix W. Pawlowski-First Aero Professor, early, 1900s (Box 13)
        - Thelma J. Peterson '37 BSE ME/ First Woman Grad From MEAM, Various (Box 13)
        - Prof. Pollock W/ IOE Classroom, 10/28/1991 (Box 13)
        - Shockley Brattain, Bardeen/ Nobel Prize Winners in Physics, 1956 (Box 13)
        - Ragone, David V., 1972-80 (Box 13)
        - President Ronald Reagan w/ Prof Donald Katz, 3/24/1983 (Box 13)
        - H. C. Sadler, older (Box 13)
        - Sadler, Walter C., 1937-41 (Box 13)
        - Scott, Norman (Box 13)
        - Skin Divers, Police, Lee Somers, Guy Meadows (Box 13)
        - Raymond J. Smit '50 BSE Civ; '55 MSE, older (Box 13)
        - Nelson Spencer/ Michigan Engineer, Fall 1984 (Box 13)
        - Roger Staubach, older (Box 13)
        - Henry Earle Riggs (1865-1947), older-1940s ? (Box 13)
        - Alexander Winchell First Prof of Engineering-Civil Eng, 1850s (Box 13)
        - DeVolson Wood Founder of Engineering Curriculum, 1860s (Box 13)
        - Van Wylen, G. J., 1960s (Box 13)
        - Misc. Students, Bulletin Photos, 1991-1992 (Box 13)
        - Misc. Students, Bulletin Photos, 1980s (Box 13)
        - Misc. Chem Lecture?, Early, 1900s (Box 13)
      - College of Engineering Staff
        - Ed Borbely-Engineering Administrator, 1995 (Box 13)
        - Stephani Bulmon-Engineering Administrator, 10/4/1991 (Box 13)
        - Brad Canale-Engineering Administrator, 9/17/1990 (Box 13)
        - Lin Cargo-Engineering Administrator, 1995 (Box 13)
        - Timothy Faley-Director of Technology Transfer and Commercialization, 3/15/2000 (Box 13)
        - Ann Gordon-Engineering Administrator, 1991 (Box 13)
        - Kurt Hill-Engineering Administrator, 1991 (Box 13)
        - James Macbain-Engineering Administrator, 1991 (Box 13)
        - Rutha Moore-Engineering Administrator, 4/1/1991 (Box 13)
        - Cynthia Redwine-Director of ECRC, 3/15/2000 (Box 13)
        - Derek Scott-Engineering Administrator, 1993 (Box 13)
        - Bobbie Simson-Engineering Administrator, 1991 (Box 13)
        - Daryl Weinert-Director of Corporate Relations, 3/15/2000 (Box 13)
        - Mary Winter-Engineering Administrator, 1991 (Box 13)
      - Student Activities
        - U of M Band & U of M Football Team, older (Box 13)
        - Concrete Canoe Team, 1982 (Box 13)
        - Dean Director Solar Car Photos (Box 13)
        - Solar Car/Sunrayce '90, 1990 (Box 13)
        - Solar Car Team '93, 1993 (Box 13)
        - Solar Car Reception, 8/1/1997 (Box 13)
        - Solar Car Team-Wash D.C., 7/1/1990 (Box 13)
        - GM Sunraycer '88, 1989 (Box 13)
        - Students/College Life in the 1960-70, 1960s (Box 13)
        - Students Studying, 3/2/1987 (Box 13)
        - Students w/ Aycock Sculpture, Late 80's (Box 13)
      - Women in Engineering (Box 14)
        - Women in Engineering/SWE Award, 10/9/1969 (Box 14)
      - Photographic Rosters of the Engineering Faculty
        - November 1960 (Box 14)
        - December 1966 (Box 14)
        - June 1967 (Box 14)
        - November 1967 (Box 14)
        - December 1968 (Box 14)
        - November 1969 (Box 14)
        - December 1971 (Box 14)
        - December 1972 (Box 14)
        - December 1973 (Box 14)
        - 1974-1975 (Box 14)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 14)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 14)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 14)
        - 1978-1979 (Box 14)
        - 1979-1980 (Box 14)
        - 1981-1983 (Box 14)
    - Student Life and School Activities (Box 9)
      - Chronological
        - circa 1967-1975, 2 folders (Box 9)
        - 1980 (Box 9)
        - Humanities, 1981 (Box 9)
        - Civil Engineering, 1982 (Box 9)
        - Japanese Seminar, 1982 (Box 9)
        - Mechanical Engineering; Whitesell, 1983 (Box 9)
        - IOE Classroom Scene, 1984 (Box 9)
        - College of Literature, Science and Art, 1986 (Box 9)
        - Fact book, 1986 (Box 9)
        - Engineering Advisory Center, 1987-1988 (Box 9)
        - Pre-Interview with Intel Corporation, 1988 (Box 9)
        - Electron Microscope Test, 1988 (Box 9)
        - Mechanical Engineering and Applied Mechanics (MEAM) Senior Design Project, 1988; 1992 (Box 9)
        - Wind tunnel, 1988 (Box 9)
        - Ergonomics Demonstration, 1989 (Box 9)
        - Michigan Engineering TV Network, 1990 (Box 9)
        - Smart Highways/Cars, 1990 (Box 9)
        - Misc. Student Portraits, 1991 (Box 9)
        - Virtual Reality, 1992 (Box 9)
        - Hovercraft Demonstration, 1993 (Box 9)
        - MJMI Interns, 1993 (Box 9)
        - Design Day, 1994 (Box 9)
        - Student Activities Career Fair, 1994 (Box 9)
        - Young America Yacht Construction, 1995 (Box 9)
        - Engineering Students in Labs, 1996-1997 (Box 9)
      - Undated
        - Aerospace Engineering, 2 folders (Box 9)
        - Balloon Launch (Box 9)
        - Chemical Engineering Students at Computer (Box 9)
        - Concrete Canoe (Box 9)
        - Conoco Presentation to Students (Box 9)
        - Engineering Yearbook (Box 9)
        - Holography Demonstration (Box 9)
        - Lectures-Contact Sheets (Box 9)
        - Misc., 4 folders (Box 9)
        - Programmed Fatigue Test (Box 9)
        - Willow Run (Box 9)
        - Yearbook (Box 9)
- Visual Material (2010 Accession)
  - Photographs, Contact Sheets and Negatives
    - Other (1980-2010)
      - Buildings
        - Gerstacker Building, 6/8/2004 (Box 15)
        - Biomedical Building construction, Gerstacker building, 11/6/2001 (Box 15)
        - Chrysler Building, 6/7/2004 (Box 15)
        - EECS Atrium, 10/16/1990 (Box 15)
        - EECS, 1997 (Box 15)
        - EECS, Fall 1991 (Box 15)
        - EECS, Dow, & Aycock Sculpture, Panorama Shots, August 1993 (Box 15)
        - LEC/Tower/Media Union, June 1997 (Box 15)
        - FXB Building, 1997 (Box 15)
        - FXB Building, 11/15/1993 (Box 15)
        - Buildings/IST, Fall 1998 (Box 15)
        - Buildings/Media Union (ITIC) Architects Drawings, February 1994 (Box 15)
        - Media Union, Construction Site Progression, January-November 1994 (Box 15)
        - Media Union/Computer Classroom, 1997 (Box 15)
        - Media Union and Flag Plaza, 1998 (Box 15)
        - North Campus Overview with New Buildings, 1994 (Box 15)
        - North Campus, Fall 1993 Panoramic, 10/12/1993-10/13/1993 (Box 15)
        - North Campus Scenes, Panoramas, 8/25/1993 (Box 15)
        - School Of Music/Earl V. Moore Building, unknown (Box 15)
        - Robert H. Lurie Center (LEC) Model, February 1994 (Box 15)
        - LEC and Lurie Tower, August 1997 (Box 15)
        - Ann and Robert H. Lurie Tower, Model, February 1994 (Box 15)
        - LEC and Lurie Tower, August 1997 (Box 15)
        - Ann and Robert H. Lurie Tower, Architectural Rendering, April 1996 (Box 15)
        - Ann and Robert H. Lurie Tower, Site Plans, April 1994 (Box 15)
        - Robert H. Lurie Engineering Center/ Lurie Tower, 1997 (Box 15)
        - Lurie Engineering Center (LEC), 1996 (Box 15)
        - (LEC), Architectural Rendering, Cr: Rochon Associates, June 1995 (Box 15)
        - Lurie Engineering Center (LEC) (Box 15)
        - Lurie Engineering Center/Tower (Box 15)
        - Phoenix Lab (Box 15)
      - Campus Landmarks (Box 16)
        - Block M Dedication, 10/13/2001 (Box 16)
        - Class of '33E Aycock Sculpture, January 1992 (Box 16)
        - Alice Aycock Sculpture-Springfest, 4/19/1994 (Box 16)
        - Sherri Smith Many Moons Painting, unknown (Box 16)
        - Wave Field, unknown (Box 16)
        - 47E Pool, Fountain, Lurie PI written in snow, 2/3/2010 (Box 16)
        - '47E Reflecting Pool "Filling,", 9/4/1997 (Box 16)
        - '47E Reflecting Pool (LEC), various (Box 16)
        - Robert H. Lurie Bust (LEC), 5/25/2001 (Box 16)
        - BEGOB, 1997 (Box 16)
        - BEGOB (Box 16)
        - Spring/ Winter Scenes, December 1997 (Box 16)
        - Shannon statue dedication, Neuhoff, Lucky, Brown, 11/9/2001 (Box 16)
        - Snelson, Aycock, Shannon bust, August 2/8/2010 (Box 16)
        - "M" block comp for cover of Fall "01 ME, August 01, 2001 (Box 16)
      - Centers, Institutes, Programs, Labs (C.I.P.L)
        - Cochlear Implant, October 2, 2010 (Box 16)
        - College Relations, Corporate Relations, Daryl We, MacBain, Sarah Cady, Tim Faley, Mike Sharer, Fall 2001 (Box 16)
      - Events
        - Artifact-150TH Display/Exhibit Artifact, 2004 (Box 16)
        - 150th Dean's Forum; Stephen Director, Peter Banks, Charles Vest, James Duderstadt, Gordon Van Wylen, David Ragone, Katherine White, 10/17/2003 (Box 16)
        - Alumni Weekend Display, unknown (Box 16)
        - Clark Nguyen Symposium/Walking Tour, 10/13/2000 (Box 16)
        - 2002 Alumni Weekend Forum on the Future, MEAW 2002, 10/25/2002 (Box 16)
        - Forum on the Future, MEAW 200, 10/12/2001 (Box 16)
        - Student/Alumni Networking Dinner, MEAW 2001 10.11.01 (Box 16)
        - MEAW 2001 Homecoming, tailgate, football, 10/11/2001 (Box 16)
        - Alumni Meeting, reunion & Tailgate, 10/19/1996 (Box 16)
        - Alumni Society Awards Dinner, 10/8/2004 (Box 16)
        - 2000 Alumni Society Awards Dinner, 10/13/2000 (Box 16)
        - Abriola/King Endowed Professorship, 6/7/2001 (Box 16)
        - Irwin Chase Plaza Dedication, 10/11/2001 (Box 16)
        - 47E Pool and Fountain Dedication, 10/31/1997 (Box 16)
        - IMSL Dedication, 5/26/1998 (Box 17)
        - DEVLEIG Foundation Lunch/ Student Activities/ GSI Award, 04/22/1998-04/23/1998 (Box 17)
        - Dinner in Honor of Robert J. Vlasic, 11/13/1997 (Box 17)
        - Walt Weber Dinner, 9/17/1997 (Box 17)
        - FXB/ Peretz Friedmann Endowed Professorship, 5/1/2000 (Box 17)
        - Shannon/ Khargonekar Endowed Professorship, 11/1/2000 (Box 17)
        - GG Brown/ Larson Endowed Professorship, 5/25/2000 (Box 17)
        - Emeritus Weekend, 2001; 06/01/2001 (Box 17)
        - Emeritus Luncheon Display Tables, 6/1/2001 (Box 17)
        - Emeritus Weekend Luncheon '00 (Class Of '50), Includes Model of Snelson Sculpture, 6/2/2000 (Box 17)
        - Emeritus Luncheon '97, 6/6/1997 (Box 17)
        - Emeritus Luncheon '98, 6/5/1998 (Box 17)
        - Wellman/Noble Faculty Development Assistant Professor Recognition Dinner, 9/23/2003 (Box 17)
        - Auhll/Cain Endowed Professorship, 4/11/2002 (Box 17)
        - Graham/ Papalambros Endowed Professorship, 5/3/2000 (Box 17)
        - O'Connor/Shin Endowed Professorship, 5/8/2002 (Box 17)
        - Scholarship/Fellowship Luncheon, 2003; 11/7/2003 (Box 17)
        - Scholarship/Fellowship Luncheon, 2002; 11/1/2002 (Box 17)
        - 2001 Endowed Scholarship and Fellowship Luncheon, Ziegler, Borchardt, Overberger, Wagener, Hirs, Caddell, Bartscht, Schmidt, Wilkes, Graham, Kidder, Culver, Flanigan, Stern, B. Williams, Brauer, Mirsky, Dodge., 11/2/2001 (Box 17)
        - Faculty Honors Dinner Dance
          - 3/27/2004 (Box 17)
          - 2/10/2001 (Box 17)
          - 4/5/2003 (Box 17)
          - 2/20/1999 (Box 17)
          - 2/21/1998 (Box 17)
        - Endowed Scholarship Luncheon '97, 11/14/1997 (Box 17)
        - Anne Monterio Retirement, 9/25/2000 (Box 18)
        - Linda Katehi Farewell Reception, 12/3/2001 (Box 18)
        - Khargonekar Farewell Reception, 06/13/2001 (Box 18)
        - Wayne Jones Reception, 10/10/2001 (Box 18)
        - Ronald Gibala William Sommers at Alumni Awards dinner, 10/7/2005 (Box 18)
        - Farewell Reception for Jim Bean, 6/3/2004 (Box 18)
        - Goff Smith Lecture Herb Kroemer, 4/16/2002 (Box 18)
        - 2005 Spring Graduation, 04/30/2005 (Box 18)
        - Graduation, Spring 2004; 5/1/2004 (Box 18)
        - 2003 Graduation, 4/26/2003 (Box 18)
        - Spring 2002 Graduation, 4/27/2002 (Box 18)
        - Graduation, 4/28/2001, Spring 2001; 2 folders (Box 18)
        - 2004 Graduation Photos Stanley Berent, William Joy, Koopmann, 5/1/2004 (Box 18)
        - FXB Groundbreaking, 11/3/1990 (Box 18)
        - FXB model inspection by Mother, 1990 (Box 18)
        - Graduation, 2000; 4/29/2000; 2 folders (Box 18)
        - 2001 Fall Parents' Weekend, D. Johnson, 11/9/2001 (Box 19)
        - Parent's Weekend Reception/ BEGOB, 10/17/1997 (Box 19)
        - Conger Check Presentation, 10/4/1999 (Box 19)
        - Conger Scholarship Award '98, 11/4/1998 (Box 19)
        - Conger Check Presentation '97/BEGOB (Close-Up); Fountain, 10/29/1997 (Box 19)
        - Excellence in Staff Service Awards (ESSA)-Reception and Portraits '97, 5/1/1997 (Box 19)
        - Excellence in Staff Service Awards, 2001; 5/10/2001 (Box 19)
        - Staff Service Awards (ESSA) 2003, 2003 various (Box 19)
        - Past Excellence in Staff Service Award Winners, Various (Box 19)
        - 2004 Student Leadership Honors Brunch, 03/14/2004 (Box 19)
        - Spencer Lecture / Vern Ehlers, 3/24/2005 (Box 19)
        - Muscat Family Parents Program, 2004; 8/27/2004 (Box 19)
        - Small Tech Symposium, 3/31-4/1/05 (Box 19)
        - Regents Meeting, 1/15/2004 (Box 19)
        - Ann Marie Sastry/ Clague Middle School Demo, 10/3/2000 (Box 19)
        - NAE Induction Reception, Linda Abriola, Richard Woods, Ron Larsen, 4/30/2003 (Box 19)
        - September 11 Teach-in, 11/8/2001 (Box 19)
        - Landes Prize Luncheon, 3/17/2004 (Box 19)
        - Mentoring Dinner, 10/30/1997 (Box 19)
        - FIPS, Tomas Zerbuchen, 2/14/2003 (Box 19)
      - Faculty Programs
        - ME Research-Vegetable Based Cutting Fluids, 8/26/2003 (Box 19)
        - Faculty Entrepreneurs-Najafi/ Wise/ Solid State Sensors, 4/1/1999 (Box 19)
        - Dekaban Fellows, 9/18/1998 (Box 19)
        - Dekaban Fund/Politechnika Warszawska, 6/1/1999 (Box 19)
        - Faculty Entrepreneurs-Levi & Maria Thompson-TJ Enterprises, 4/1/1999 (Box 19)
        - Frontiers in Education and Research 01, 05/30/1920-05/31/1920 (Box 19)
        - Warsaw U-Tech VIP's Photo Op s. Director, 3/13/2001 (Box 19)
      - Individuals A-Z
        - Anniversary Task Force/ Jerry Levin, S. Director, Don Graham, Kevin O'Connor, C. Robert Kidder, M. O'Donnell, Susan Feagin, 12/8/1999 (Box 19)
        - Alumni Award Recipients-Charles M. Vest, Anthony M. Fadell, Charles S. Hutchins, Karl G. Bartscht, David J. Dewitt, William W. Graessley, Marshall G. Jones, John R. (Chip) Keough, Thomas A. Mehlhorn, Martin G. Mlynczak, Robert G. Radwin, Lester Rosenblatt, Kenneth H. Stokoe Ii, Jack L. Walker, Charla Ann (Kamm) Wise, 2004 (Box 19)
        - Alumni Society Award Recipients W. P. Cherry, J. Collins, P. Genalis, J. Levine, A. Nicholas, B. Oakley, R. Patton, G. Ponce De Leon, W. Rhines, M. Stonebraker, R. Trew, P. Turinsky, H. C. Walker, J. Macks, E. Aupperle, 2003 (Box 19)
        - Alumni Society Merit Award Recipients Paul Kern, Larry Page, John Holt, Claudia Alexander, Thomas Brady, Stuart Churchill, Erhan inlar, Stephen Debrock, Paul Freedman, Steven Goldstein, Ernest Jacquet, Michael Korybalski, Ellen Leonard, Kevin O'Connor, Rob Rutenbar, Various, 2002 (Box 19)
        - Alumni Society Merit Award Recipients '01/John Carpenter, Robert Graham, Ray Judson, Irma Wyman, Hun Chol Kim, Bruce Nourse, Tenho Connable, Chris Dingle, Leo Donner, Roger Kallock, Jack Lousma (Box 19)
        - Alumni Society Merit Award Recipients 2000/J. Cashman, F. Gibbons, K. Jones, Wm. Joy, J. Muckstadt, A. Nuttall, C. O'Melia, M. Pettibone, A. Rowe, E. Shearer, G. Smith, S. Solomon, C. Vest (Box 19)
        - Alumni Society Merit Award Recipients Paul Bigby, Robt Brown, L. Evans, James Fici, Robt. Fuhrman, Frank Iarossi, Gloria Jeff, E. Kirkendall, Bernard Lacroute, Greg McPherson, J. Mellor, Robt. Transou, Joe Tribbia, 1999 (Box 19)
        - Alumni Society Merit Award Recipients 1998/Manuel Del Valle, Vincent Drnevich, Arnold Galloway, Vincent Gorguze, Wm. Heetderks, Robt. Kramek, Jerry Levin, James McDivitt, Ralph Reins, M. John Robinson, John Tishman, Ward Winer, Jeng-Hwa Yee (Box 19)
        - Alumni Society Merit Award Recipients 1997/Clement Arrison, Dean Hanink, Robert Hirsch, Louis Dehmlow, James Hubbell, Walter Olson, G. Keith Richey, James Russell Iii, Wm. Sommers, Philip Spaulding, John Utley, Jr., Robert Vlasic (Box 19)
        - Alumni Society Merit Award Recipients 1996/Richard Auhll, James Engels, Jerome Goldman, Charles Hutchins, Thomas Keinath, Peter Lederman, David Liddle, Thomas Ryan, Peter Schmidt, Jr., Theo Sharp, J. Hunter Waite, Jr. (Box 19)
        - Alumni Society Merit Award Recipients 1995/Eugene Bierly, David Breiholz, J.H. Brophy, Peter Fuss, James Goodrich, Carroll Haas, Ieum Ieumwananonthachai, Emerson Kampen, C. Robert Kidder, Robt. Stephenson, George Skurla, Gordon Van Wylen (Box 19)
        - Alumni Society Merit Award Recipients 1994/Curtis Bottum Jr., Frederick Buckman, John Couch, Raymond Decker, Gerald Keeler, Tawfig Khowry, Wyun Lee, Roger McCarthy, David Messerschmitt, John Warner, J. Louis York (Box 20)
        - Alumni Society Merit Award Recipients 1993/Arden Bement Jr., Robert Buckler, Samuel Fuller, Jerome Goldman, Phillip Hall, Willis Hawkins, Richard Jelinek, George Pilko, Raymond Roble, Hans Weichsel Jr., Sidney Yip (Box 20)
        - Alumni Society Merit Award Winner 1992 Richard Balzhiser, 1988-1992 (Box 20)
        - Richard Auhll, 1992 (Box 20)
        - Harry Benford (Box 20)
        - Lee Bollinger Past U-M President, unknown (Box 20)
        - President Lee Bollinger w/ Dept. Chairs, 7/1/1997 (Box 20)
        - Harm Buning, 9/12/1991 (Box 20)
        - Arthur W. Burkes (Box 20)
        - Diane Burton, Olympian Sailing Entry, 1992 (Box 20)
        - Edmund Carpenter CEO General Signal, unknown (Box 20)
        - Matt Cavanaugh, 8/15/2002 (Box 20)
        - Carl Clare, BSE '25, 1990 (Box 20)
        - Dekaban Scholars, 6/22/1999 (Box 20)
        - Robert Denner Family-Robert, Nancy and Jim Denner, 6/13/2002 (Box 20)
        - Dean Director, 2004 (Box 20)
        - Mary C. Dirkes, unknown (Box 20)
        - Charles C Dybvig, '31 BSE A&A (Box 20)
        - Harold Eberhardt, 6/1/1992 (Box 20)
        - Anthony England, Astronaut, unknown (Box 20)
        - Excellence In Staff Service Awards Portraits 2000/Susan Ederer; Karen Richardson, Shirley McCoy; Anne Monterio; Clark Nguyen, 5/3/2000 (Box 20)
        - Excellence in Staff Service Award (ESSA) Recipients: Janet Kemp-Grenier, Henia Kamil, Kathy Stolaruk, Kelly Cormier, Deb Swartz, unknown (2000 ?) (Box 20)
        - Excellence in Staff Service Awards Portraits, 04/18/2001 (Box 20)
        - David Finley, Summer 2001 (Box 20)
        - Donald N. Frey, unknown (Box 20)
        - Roberta Gutman, unknown (Box 20)
        - Robert T. Hall, Alumni Aero E42, First Trust Systems, unknown (Box 20)
        - Elaine Harden, 9/15/2003 (Box 20)
        - Todd Herrick, unknown (Box 20)
        - Michael Hess, unknown (Box 20)
        - Jon Holt Family, 9/25/1998 (Box 20)
        - R. M. Howe (Box 20)
        - Stefan Humphries BSE ES '84, unknown (Box 20)
        - INTEL Representatives and Labs Sponsored By INTEL, 1/1995 (Box 20)
        - Ashoo Jain, 1/2001 (Box 20)
        - Marshall Jones, Summer 2001 (Box 20)
        - William/ Bill Joy 03, May 20, 2000 (Box 20)
        - Vyto Kauneli BSE CEE '76, MSE '84, unknown (Box 20)
        - Robert Kidder, 2/17/2003 (Box 20)
        - Maxine Kumin, CoE Roger M. Jones Poet in Residence, 1996 (Box 20)
        - Bernard and Ronni Lacroute, 11/1/2004 (Box 20)
        - Ann Lurie, 1994 (Box 20)
        - Sam Zell & Robert Lurie (Box 20)
        - Thomas L. Magnanti, unknown (Box 20)
        - Jon Malkovich 1999 UMEC President, 4/1999 (Box 20)
        - Jyoti Mazumder and Antoine Naaman, 8/15/2002 (Box 20)
        - Jim McDivitt (Alumnus), 1962; 1993 (Box 20)
        - John Mitchell BSE ME '85, Arthur Kohn BSE M '34, 4/7/2005 (Box 20)
        - Keith Newburry, 7/1/2001 (Box 20)
        - Greg Opas, (ABS Award Winner), 5/19/1992 (Box 20)
        - Kevin O'Connor, 2000 (Box 20)
        - Larry Page, Spring 2001 (Box 20)
        - Robert Pinsky, CoE, Roger M. Jones Poet in Residence, 1995 (Box 20)
        - Ros Potter, '07 Eng. (Box 20)
        - Dan Schimpf, 2/20/2003 (Box 20)
        - Robert Scott Portrait, 6/29/2002 (Box 20)